Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Gotti took this man
for no good reason.
[grunts]
He's convinced that your guy
may have something to do
with Vincent Zaccaro's
disappearance.
I'm gonna need you to put
a bullet in Flanagan's head.
[gunshot]
Jimmy. I told you what to do.
He's my friend. Eamon.
And he's one of us.
Those Irish bastards are
responsible for this.
I need those Irish bastards.
I can run the Javits.
I would consider
letting you do that.
But you've been a naughty boy.
Apparently. some
of Castellano's captains
are going against his wishes.
trafficking in narcotics.
The club is a front
for a Colombian
distribution network.
We don't sling warehouse
orders to strangers.
I work for Vincent Zaccaro.
[Sweeney]
But if you want Mickey back.
I think this is your best bet.
[Jimmy] I have to send
a message to the Colombians.
"Do not sell cocaine
to John Gotti."
-This is fucking suicide!
-Yeah. I know.
But what other choice do I have?
I do have a wee favor
to ask you.
I have a package
that I need kept safe.
-How many warheads are there?
-There's just one.
Drugs are dirty and dangerous.
Sean!
[shouting]
[Paul] I'm not gonna
jeopardize everything
I've built for a quick buck.
All due respect.
drugs are here to stay.
And if we don't sell 'em.
somebody else will.
Stop!
Took a souvenir.
Our timeline has been ramped up.
Soon I'll be taking
that weapon off your hands.
There was a murder
of a cop in Massachusetts.
The killer is the kind of man
my son admires.
Well. at least
one good thing came out of it.
I killed a cop.
[Glenn] Worse than that.
the kind of man
my son could someday become.
I know who killed that cop.
It was fuckin' Pat Murphy.
What makes you say that?
You're gonna fuckin' tell me.
-I'll make it go away.
-How much?
I just want you
to leave my boy Danny alone.
In return...
[grunts]
I'll handle Pat Murphy.
[gasping]
[Father Michael] We commend
our brother to God's mercy.
Trusting that.
even in death. there is grace.
Judge not lest ye be judged.
the Bible teaches us.
This applies
not only to men's deeds.
but to the mysterious works
of the Lord.
Pat Murphy was a dear friend...
a son...
and soon-to-be father.
And although
the Lord has called him back.
we thank Him for the time
we did have with Pat.
And entrust Pat's soul...
to His eternal care.
May the Earth
receive him gently.
[all] The Father. the Son.
and the Holy Spirit. amen.
[mournful Irish music playing]
[punk rock theme music]
-♪ It didn't take long ♪
-♪ I didn't get far ♪
♪ Before the cops were told ♪
-♪ That I'd stolen the car ♪
-♪ Stolen the car ♪
-♪ There was an APB ♪
-♪ APB ♪
-♪ Sent out for me ♪
-♪ Out for me ♪
♪ Ratted out by my own ♪
♪ Now I'm a public enemy ♪
♪ I'm a Catholic school kid ♪
-♪ I'm an altar boy ♪
-♪ Altar boy ♪
♪ I was dropped on my head ♪
-♪ Now I'm here to destroy ♪
-♪ Here to destroy ♪
-♪ I'm a stone-cold killer ♪
-♪ Stone-cold killer ♪
-♪ In the CYO ♪
-♪ CYO ♪
♪ I'm lining them up ♪
♪ And I'm laying them low ♪
♪ But honest as the day
is long that's a fact ♪
♪ I'm not nearly half
as bad as I act ♪
♪ See. I'm always wrong
in the eyes of the law ♪
♪ Parents and priests say
it's the final straw ♪
♪ But sure as the sun.
it rises and sets ♪
♪ I'll do it again.
it's a surefire bet ♪
Good Lord.
you guys see Pat's ex?
That bun in the oven
looked about to burst.
I didn't know
Pat was gonna be a father.
Did any of you?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah. of course.
She kicked him out 'cause
he didn't want to marry her.
She woulda taken him back.
It's a tough break for the kid.
Why don't you raise
the kid. Mick. huh?
You look like
you're ready to be a father.
Fuck off.
[Jimmy]
What I'd like to know
is who the fuck would do Pat
in our own backyard?
Yeah.
[car door closing]
Sweeney. Breen.
Boss.
Sad day.
Sad day indeed.
Any word yet?
Word is there were
some Puerto Ricans
looking for trouble
in the neighborhood that night.
So... we're lookin' into it.
Take care.
[car starting]
Come on.
Let's go get a drink.
[Irish folk music playing]
♪ I ♪
♪ Haven't seen you in a while ♪
♪ I sigh ♪
♪ Miss your little smile ♪
♪ Never told you ♪
♪ I loved you in a while ♪
♪ Wish I was back home ♪
♪ Again ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
One for Pat!
[all] For Pat!
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah. now ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I tell ya ♪
[singer] Miss you.
We love you.
[overlapping chatter]
[Irish folk music playing]
Cliffie!
Hey! Hey!
Lads. lads. lads!
Ciúnas! Ciúnas!
Connor. Connor. Shut up.
[Sweeney]
Thank you. Cliffie.
When I was growing up
here in Hell's Kitchen...
I could walk Ninth Avenue
from 50th Street
down to 34th Street...
say hello
to every soul I encountered.
Man. woman and child by name.
Times change.
Lot of faces have changed.
Some of us have grown old
beyond recognition.
[crowd laughing]
Some are gone.
What I'm trying to say is...
doesn't matter
if it's your best friend...
your family...
or somebody you don't even know.
When we lose someone
from the neighborhood...
-we all feel it.
-[door opening]
Pat Murphy was part of what
makes this neighborhood great.
And our best tribute to him...
is to continue to thrive.
That's what Pat would want.
So. here's to Pat Murphy.
and all of us
who hold him in our hearts.
To Paddy.
Slàinte.
[all cheering]
Be right back.
[music and chatter]
[overlapping chatter]
-Had a little talk with Danny.
-Yeah?
Told him he's not
working for me anymore.
-like you asked me to.
-I appreciate that.
It's a little more complicated.
How so?
He thinks you had something
to do with Pat Murphy's death.
Oh. what the fuck.
Wait. he said that?
He says you basically beat
the information out of him.
and then after that.
Pat shows up dead on the street.
Nah. I gave him
a fucking smack
'cause he was running
a smart mouth.
Whatever. If he starts talking
to Pat's friends about it.
that's not gonna be
good for you.
More importantly. the boys think
I had anything to do with it.
that's not gonna be good for me.
which is also not good for you.
-Understood?
-Yeah. yeah.
What do you want me to do?
Convince your kid
you had nothing to do with it.
Yeah. convince him how?
Whatever the fuck. Glenn.
I don't know.
I'm not the dad. you are.
Figure it out.
How much we got so far. Jimmy?
[Jimmy]
About 480.
Make it an even five.
Shit. we're gonna need more.
Look. Jimmy.
we all know
where we can get more money.
A lot more.
We're sitting
on a fortune. Jimmy.
Mr. Sweeney has forbidden us
from selling drugs.
So why'd you take 'em
out of the disco. then?
I'm hoping to change his mind.
Go by yourself.
I'm out.
What're you talking about?
Sweeney wants us
to collect the numbers.
We're gonna be late.
Sweeney doesn't want to see me.
Why?
It's my stupid dad.
He's bustin' my balls.
But fuck him.
I'll change Sweeney's mind.
I can't even fuckin'
fasten these pants.
-let 'em out an inch.
-Yes. Mr. Sweeney.
I weigh the exact same
as the last time
I wore this fucking monkey suit.
-How is my belly bigger?
-I guess your waist's
been drinking pints
behind your back again.
[phone ringing]
Possible your trousers
just shrunk. Mr. Sweeney.
Smart man.
Eddie. I'm gonna replace you
with Mr. Quinn here.
Great. He'd be doing us both
a fucking favor then.
[laugh]
Sorry to interrupt.
No worries.
We're just...
getting me ready
for the big night.
He's being honored
by the Hibernian Society.
Lifetime Achievement Award.
Aren't you a bit young for that?
Please don't flatter him.
his head's big enough.
Just like his fucking waistline.
-[soft chuckle]
-So. what's the award for?
Uh. it's for someone
who embodies Irish heritage.
Catholic values.
and public service.
[Dukey] Translation. someone
who will make a large donation
to one of their charities.
Yeah. everybody's got
their fuckin' hands
in my pockets.
Welcome to my world.
Jimmy. listen. have the boys
pass out some of those.
uh. the invites. yeah?
I don't expect
you hoi polloi to come.
it's 50 bucks a plate.
Well. actually. there was...
there was something
I wanted to talk to you about.
-Can we speak in private?
-[Sweeney] Yeah.
Give me a minute.
I'll meet you outside.
[sighs]
Fucking thing.
[Jimmy] First of all.
I just. I want to say thank you.
for what you did for Mickey.
[Sweeney]
How's he feeling?
Ah. he's... he's sore.
I think he kinda likes the pain.
I admire the way
you stood up for Flanagan.
It pissed me off...
but I understand.
You know. a man gets to be
my age. you start thinking
about certain things.
Do I care about
this award? No.
But it does symbolize
something important.
And that's.
you sum up a man's life.
you want to know
what he stood for. right?
Now. I don't give half a shit
about the Hibernian Society.
but I care about
this neighborhood.
So. what'd you want
to come see me about?
That Starship job
Castellano gave us.
Look. I know you share
his feelings about dealing coke
and I get it.
I do...
but if we don't deal it.
someone else will.
I mean. they already are.
and whoever does.
they'll just become stronger
and more of a threat to us.
Why are we having
this conversation. Jimmy?
Because I took six kilos
from that disco
before we burned it down.
Fuck! Jesus Christ.
Zip that shit up.
Goddamnit!
Look. we could use the money
to help Pat's ma and his kid.
If it even is his fucking kid.
To be frank with you. Eamon.
you know. you're giving
all this money away
to charity. which is great.
but me and the boys are
kinda hurtin' for cash.
And this...
this Javits Center is
all well and good for you but...
This Javits Center is gonna
help all of us. okay?
-It's bringing in millions...
-Yeah. no. I know...
Unless... Unless
you fuck it up dealing drugs.
The Feds are handing out
30-year sentences for narcotics.
So. somebody gets busted.
they're gonna fucking flip.
That's why Big Paul is
against it and I am too.
With all due respect. Eamon.
you can't stop cocaine
from taking over.
Demand's too great.
And I think it's worth the risk.
You fucking shot Zaccaro
against my wishes.
and good riddance.
fuck that guy.
We're still trying to clean up
that fucking mess. okay?
Don't go against me on this.
I'm gonna fuckin' burn
this shit.
-But I'm just... I...
-Look. we don't
fucking deal drugs.
Period. Understood?
Yes. sir.
Make sure your crew
gets that message.
[Italian music playing on radio]
I've been leaning
on the Dominicans
and the Harlem crews.
Everybody knows
something went down...
but nobody knows
who stole your cocaine.
We need fucking answers.
You tell every corner boy
from Jamaica to Jerome
that if so much as
a gram of my coke shows up.
I want to know where. when.
and who's holding it.
-Absolutely.
-And you let them know that
any stupid motherfucker
caught trying to sell
my product. they're gonna die.
I understand.
Whoever fucking robbed you
knew to use Zaccaro's name.
So. if you ask me.
it's Big Paul.
sending a message
through the back door.
and using those fuckin'
Micks as pawns.
-Backstabbing cocksucker.
-He's got brass fucking balls.
Yeah.
One day. I'm gonna
shove them up his ass.
Now. fuck off.
[tense music]
[knocking on door]
Hello. Moira.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I need to talk to Danny.
He here?
He's in school.
School?
Yeah. That's what
he tells me anyway.
When will he be home?
No idea.
But he won't want to see you.
I can tell ya that right now.
Okay.
Can we talk. please?
It's been a long time.
Please? It's important.
Five minutes.
Jacob's Biscuits?
Where'd you find those?
There's a place on 23rd Street.
Danny picks 'em up for me.
So he says he's going to school?
He's not.
He's hanging out
with Irish gangsters
on the West Side.
To be honest. I don't know
where the hell he goes.
He came back last week
with his face busted up.
and he wouldn't tell me
what happened.
He barely says
a word to me. but...
he buys me these biscuits
'cause he knows that I like 'em.
And Eileen liked them too.
Yeah. They were her favorite.
So. I been trying.
I've been trying to form
some kind of
a relationship with him.
It's a bit late for that.
Yeah. well.
maybe you could help me.
How could I help you?
You know. better question.
why the fuck should I help you?
I haven't seen you
since my sister's funeral.
You think it's been
a pleasure raising that boy?
Every birthday. Christmas...
every anniversary
of my sister's death. and...
not a fucking peep out of you.
I can't change that.
Let me try and fix things.
Right.
[door shutting]
[sighs]
Look who came by to say hello.
-[Sweeney] Look at this shit.
-[Breen] What the fuck?
Right? So. if this is pure.
it's gotta be worth.
I don't know.
three. four hundred grand...
a lot of fuckin' money.
I thought you told Jimmy
that we weren't gonna...
Yeah. if the young guys
start selling this shit.
it's gonna go tits up for sure.
This is one time only.
And what if
Castellano finds out?
Fuck Big Paul.
He's a hypocrite.
He gets kick-ups
on the same drugs
he forbids Gotti from selling.
I guess that makes us
hypocrites then. doesn't it?
[exhales]
Yeah. I guess it does.
Maybe I'll donate mine
to the Hibernian Society.
feed the poor Irish.
What are you gonna do
with the rest?
Don't worry. Eddie.
you'll get your cut.
Yeah.
Get a hold of Leon. will ya?
Tell him I wanna see him.
Okay.
[door shutting]
[Glenn] Hey.
I owe you an apology.
More than one.
Let me see your face.
You know. my old man used
to hit me a lot growing up.
That's not an excuse.
It's just all I know.
I'll let you in
on a little secret.
I hate myself more
than you could ever hate me.
I'm sorry. Danny.
What I just don't understand is.
why'd you leave?
When your mother
and I got together.
I... I'd just come back
home from the war.
I-I-I was broken.
I think she was
a little broken. too.
Both of us were drinking hard.
and she got into drugs.
Heroin.
I left.
I fucking left.
I left you behind
with her fuckin' sister.
and I hate myself
for doing that.
But you are my son.
And I love you
with all that I am.
And I would do anything
to protect you from harm.
Do you understand that?
Did you kill Pat?
No.
Homicide guys said it was...
some spics did it
over a dope deal.
This is why I'm sayin'
stay off the streets.
do your schoolwork.
Be good.
Don't end up like Pat.
I'm tired.
[Glenn] All right.
It's okay I come back.
visit you again sometime?
[rock music playing
on headphones]
What's the soonest we can safely
move that package off the docks?
That's why I. uh.
asked you here.
What is it?
I went to check on it
last night.
and it was missing.
And sometimes they clear out
the unused cargo crates.
unbeknownst to me.
and that is probably
what happened.
Are you fuckin' jokin' me?
[Bridget] I'm sorry. Brendan.
It's gone. and it's
probably in a landfill.
which is good 'cause it means
it won't be discovered.
and it will not be
traced back...
[bartender]
Need a hand. Bridget?
Yeah. best not to make a scene.
Is that why you brought me here?
What'd you think I was gonna do?
Put a fuckin' gun in your mouth?
'Cause you're right.
That's exactly
what I fuckin' would have done.
Yeah. I wouldn't
put it past ya.
Do you realize
what a major fuck-up this is?
Well. I don't know
what your plan is.
but I'm sure
you'll figure a way around it.
[scoffs]
You're some
piece of work. aren't you?
What I was doing wasn't
just for Ireland.
It was for you.
What're you talking about?
[Brendan]
My target.
The British operative.
flying into New York
from Belfast.
Colonel Gerald Markham.
The man who killed your parents.
Can't believe we're back
to this nickel-and-dime shit.
Yeah. business as usual.
It's fucked up.
I mean. that coke could
be worth 300 grand.
that's before we even cut it.
A lot of us could use
that kind of fuckin' money.
Hey. you're alive. right?
And that's 'cause of who?
-You.
-No. not just me.
If Sweeney hadn't gone
to Castellano. you'd be dead.
so don't forget that.
If he wants us to do a job.
we do it.
He's the fuckin' boss.
Not you. Not me.
[doorbell jingling]
Hello. Finn.
Boys. How may I help you?
You know why we're here.
Uh. Mr. Sweeney will have
his money by next Tuesday.
Yeah. you said that
last Tuesday.
[Finn] I meant
the Tuesday after this.
[Mickey]
What you got there?
These fuckin' dog tags?
Are you selling these?
You can put your name
on the blank ones.
Yeah. I got some already.
So do my buddies.
half of them lyin'
in a fucking jungle right now!
-You fucking cocksucker!
-Hey. hey. hey.
Calm down.
All right?
Look. look.
my bookie ran off with my money.
You shouldn't be betting
on the fuckin' horses. Finn.
Do you remember
what I said last time?
-[Finn] Yeah.
-No money.
I'm gonna have
to break your thumbs.
Or I'm gonna cut 'em off
with this.
Look. be reasonable. Jimmy.
I have a tip for you
at Aqueduct!
Give me your hands. Finn.
-It's 35 to one!
-Hands. Finn! Let's go.
Give him your fuckin' hands!
[shouting in pain]
I knew your mother!
She was a very good woman!
I used to see her at Holy Cross!
Hey. you better
shut the fuck up.
or I'm putting this knife
right up your ass.
Please!
Fuck it.
[gasps]
What are you doin'?
[Jimmy]
See what we got here.
Twelve bucks?
The fuck kinda business
you runnin' here. Finn?
Jesus.
I am gonna give you
one more day.
And you at least
come up with the vig.
Do you understand?
No more bettin'
on the fuckin' horses.
I promise.
Bless you. Jimmy!
Take whatever you want
from the shop!
Fuck you!
Just come up with the money.
I see these on sale again.
you're fucking dead.
[doorbell jingling]
[tense music]
Eamon Sweeney
with six fucking keys.
Gotta say I was surprised.
Came my way
as payback for a debt.
What. motherfucker
just handed you six bricks?
[sighing] The motherfucker
is sitting in Rikers.
looking at five to ten.
This is all he had to give.
Hmm.
You was always so fucking
strict about no dope.
In this case. I got no choice.
Since we're in business together
with the shylocking
and the numbers.
I know you're a man I can trust.
Now that is correct.
My man.
How's the purity?
It's over 95 percent.
Hoo. Shit.
You didn't get it
from me. right?
[Leon] You dealing powder?
Who the fuck is
going to believe me anyway?
Yo. Charlie.
we was never here. right?
No. sir.
Okay. so how much?
-Twenty a key.
-Get the fuck.
We're not fuckin'
idiots here. Leon.
That stuff goes wholesale
at least 50. 55 a kilo.
Hm. So. you a big
cocaine man now?
Yeah.
[chuckling]
Forty's what I pay
when it comes shrink-wrapped
from Medellin
with a priest's blessing.
Give you 40 apiece
for the first five.
35 for everything after that.
Won't be any more after this.
Who did you get this from again?
-Fuck off.
-[chuckling]
-Always good to see you. Eamon.
-Yeah.
Be seein' you.
[door opening]
[door shutting]
[horn honking]
[tense music]
-Oh. fuck. sorry!
-[Mickey] Hey. princess!
Uh. Erin here was just
helping me with my recovery.
She's doin'
a splendid job. actually.
Yeah. yeah. is Jimmy here?
-He's just in the bedroom.
-Okay.
[giggles]
What are you tryin' to do?
You trying to get me
-kicked outta here?
-[laughing]
Do you know
what's going on out there?
Yeah. what do you think
I've been listening to
for the past hour?
Hi.
[distant moaning]
Yeah. I know.
Bit of a mood kill.
[exhales]
So. uh...
I. I. I talked to Cahill.
-Oh. yeah?
-Yeah.
And did he buy our story?
Yeah.
Yeah. He was angry.
but it's nothing I can't handle.
It turns out
he doesn't need the weapon
to complete the mission.
But he does need me.
Have you lost your fuckin' mind?
Can't you see what he's trying
to do. he's tryin' to get
-in your fucking head?
-Jimmy. Stop. stop!
It's not. not for Cahill.
and it is not for Ireland.
This is my choice.
I am doing this for me.
What does that even mean?
Okay. all right.
it's for you. then.
Just tell me
what you're doing. then.
I can't.
Why not?
Because you'll try and stop me.
I never ask you
to explain the things you do.
and the same goes for me.
You and I...
we have to trust each other.
But this is
fucking dangerous. Bridget.
And what you do isn't?
[distant loud moaning]
Well. it sounds like
they're fuckin' in love.
Just promise me
you'll come back to me.
I fucking promise.
[Gotti]
Are you sure about that?
Eamon Sweeney himself
sold it to Leon?
That's right.
So why the fuck are
you here and not Leon?
He got a good deal
on that shit. man.
He wasn't asking any questions.
[laughing]
That motherfucker.
How do we know
it's the same fuckin' stuff?
Hmm?
I don't trust this nigger.
I figured you would say
something like that.
all disrespectful and shit
while I'm here risking my ass
with Leon for being here.
trying to help you
motherfuckers.
Hey Phil. watch your mouth.
Got proof?
Sure as fuck do.
I snagged this wrap...
when Leon and the boys
were cutting it up.
That's the Colombian
stamp. right?
That's the shit that was
dealt out of the Starship.
Yeah. that's the same packaging.
All right. Charlie.
You done good.
How good?
Quack. give him five Gs.
Ten would be better.
Yeah. listen.
how 'bout I keep my money
and you don't walk outta here?
Damn. you boys don't know
how to take a joke.
[door opening]
So. what's our next move?
Kill that motherfucker
Eamon Sweeney.
[psychedelic rock music]
Motherfucker.
What was that about?
Apparently. you didn't do
a very good job
-convincing your kid.
-The fuck did he say?
He thinks I gave the order
and you killed Pat Murphy.
Son of a bitch.
I told him
I had nothin' to do with it.
Yeah. He also said
he doesn't care.
He'll keep his mouth shut
if I take him back.
Basically. your kid is fuckin'
blackmailing me here. Glenn.
I'll talk to him again.
Straighten him out.
Will you now?
Yeah. yeah.
I don't have time for this shit.
If I see Danny
around the neighborhood...
I might have
to shut him up myself.
That's my son
you're talkin' about.
Yeah. And if you want
to keep him alive...
keep him out of Hell's Kitchen.
I won't be having
this conversation again.
[tense music]
[Mickey]
I fuckin' hate this place.
It's like
a gift shop for yuppies
to buy our shit
so they can feel tough.
We should burn this place
to the ground
with that motherfucker
inside it.
Fuckin' why'd you go easy
on that guy?
-Hey. Jimmy?
-What?
You hear what I said?
I said. why'd you let him off?
I don't know.
He knew my ma
before she got sick.
Oh.
She was a nice lady.
your mother.
Always good to me.
It's a shame your father
was a fuckin' asshole.
[doorbell jingling]
Uh. boys. I thought
you'd give me till evening.
Oh. for Christ's sake. Finn.
I already gave you a break.
[Finn] Look. look.
look. my cousin
from New Jersey is comin'.
He's gonna lend me the money.
Oh. look. I've already
gotten $50 here. Look. see?
Just stop it
with the fucking bullshit.
I promise you.
it is not helping.
And gimme your fucking hands.
I'm... I'll have it
by tonight. I swear.
Gimme your fuckin' hands!
[shouting in pain]
I'll make it fast. okay?
Your Mr. Sweeney
just donated $100.000
to the Hibernian Society.
and he's going to need
my lousy 250 by tonight?
It ain't fair. Jimmy!
Where'd he get
that kind of money?
What the fuck'd you just say?
Yeah. yeah. $100.000 in cash
because they're giving him
some goddamn award!
Everybody's talkin' about it!
Are you fuckin' lying to me?
No. Jimmy.
Bandage your thumbs
like I broke 'em
and don't take 'em off
for three weeks.
Do you hear?
Thank you.
Thank you. Jimmy!
I'll have the money by tonight!
Just... just get it
when you can.
[Finn] Okay.
Do you think
Sweeney sold our coke?
Fuck yeah. I do.
Now. Greg Scarpa
vouched for you boys.
so I know you're pros.
but you go straight back
to Philly when you're done...
no fucking hanging around.
We can do this tomorrow night.
We know where he's gonna be.
Been advertising it
all around town.
[Gotti]
Hibernian Award Dinner?
That's perfect.
Give them shanty
Irish motherfuckers
something they can
really celebrate.
John...
you sure you wanna do this?
Well. I didn't stutter. did I?
Big Paul has
an agreement with Sweeney.
-It may rattle him.
-Paul can suck my dick.
John. just...
think this through.
[Gotti] What. do I look
like I give a shit?
I put up 50K for that shipment.
Now. I'm out of pocket
and I gotta kick up to Paul
no matter what? What the fuck?
-I'm just sayin'...
-And I'm just saying.
keep that shit to yourself.
You boys good?
I want a phone call
when you get back to Philly.
I wanna know
this cocksucker's dead.
You said it was important.
I need help with Danny.
I want him pulled off
the street. sent to rehab.
I don't care where.
Arizona. Maine. Anywhere.
-Just out of New York City.
-Why?
Sweeney's paranoid.
He thinks Danny stole from him
but he didn't.
but it doesn't matter.
Sweeney told
the bartender at the 596
he's gonna put a bullet in Danny
I don't get him out
of the Kitchen.
Let me be clear
on what you're asking me.
You want me to arrest your son?
No. I can position that.
What I need from you is
to use your influence
with the authorities
to get him out of town.
You're asking me
to use federal pull
to ship your kid to a safe house
disguised as a clinic?
Yeah. won't look good if the son
of one of your informants
turns up in the East River.
What do I get?
I think there's a connection
between Sweeney. Castellano.
and that fire
at the Starship disco.
Got any proof?
I'm workin' on it.
But not if I'm burying my kid.
Location I can't promise.
but I'll see what I can do.
You fuck me on this.
I'll let the kid rot.
I owe you.
Yeah. you do.
[rock music playing]
You're too fucking
trustin'. Jimmy.
Fuck off.
Problem is. you put
Sweeney on a pedestal.
We all did. but now we know
he don't fuckin' belong there.
What are you.
a fuckin' shrink now?
Well. you ain't gotta be
a fuckin' shrink. Jimmy.
Any idiot can see that this
motherfucker is out for himself.
I just can't believe
I couldn't see it before.
But now. we got to accept it.
Look. brother. I get it.
Right. the guy's done
a lot for you.
After what happened with
your mother. taking you in.
putting a roof over your head.
that's not nothing.
And what? I'm not supposed
to be fuckin' grateful for that?
Sure.
But understand it
for what it is.
He has your loyalty. right?
You would die for
that motherfucker. I know you.
You think
he'd say the same for you?
He wouldn't. and he never will.
-I can't believe that.
-Jimmy.
the guy showed us who he is.
He's a fuckin' criminal.
through and through.
He pretends he's some fancy
fuckin' do-gooder. you know.
walking around in his suits
and bowin' to old ladies.
givin' his speeches
about the neighborhood.
telling everybody
and their mother.
oh. no. we don't sell narcotics.
No. that's not in our streets.
that's a dirty business.
But then what does he do?
He sells our product
and uses the money for himself.
it makes me fuckin' sick!
I just can't believe
he lied to my fuckin' face.
Right. but he did.
Jimmy. this is
the same motherfucker
that killed Davey O'Brien.
and he wanted you to shoot me.
And you know what?
I haven't heard shit about Pat
since he said
he was lookin' into it.
I'm just saying.
now we know
that this motherfucker
ain't one of us.
So what am I supposed to do?
Hmm?
You know. what if we're wrong?
What if he didn't sell the coke?
He just... He just donated
that money from his...
from his savings.
[scoffs]
Right...
and I hear there's
a bridge in Brooklyn for sale.
You know. you got a heart
of fuckin' gold. Jimmy.
Don't ever lose that. Please.
But don't give it
to a motherfucker
who don't deserve it either.
Where're you going?
I'm going
to that fuckin' dinner.
And I'm gonna make him
tell me the fuckin' truth.
[loud slam]
[Glenn]
Jacob's Biscuits.
He's in his room.
[rock music playing
through headphones]
Hey! Hey!
Take those fuckin' things off.
-What the hell do you want?
-What are you doing
hanging around with Sweeney?
You shouldn't be doing that.
What. does that
make you nervous?
I understand he told you
to stay away from him.
You honestly expect me
to believe that bullshit
you were spilling the other day?
About how some Puerto Rican guy
who killed Pat Murphy?
Oh. he magically gets killed
after you beat
the shit out of me!
Oh. what? You think
-Sweeney and I killed Pat?
-Who cares?
-I just want my job back!
-You're playin' with fire!
I'm tryin' to protect you!
I can take care of myself!
No. you can't!
In fact. I know you can't!
Leave me alone. and stay
the fuck out of my life!
Yeah. okay.
All right. tough guy.
What's this?
Hmm?
What. are you selling this shit?
Or you just using it?
What the fuck are you doing?
That's not mine!
You know what?
One day. you're gonna
thank me for this.
Fuck you!
[tense music]
Any chatter?
Not yet.
I want you to meet the others.
Mary!
Now. you've all heard
of the girl in the grey coat.
Now you're lookin' at her.
This is Sarah McKenna.
AKA Bridget Walsh.
This is
Tadhg McKenna's daughter.
Now. she's currently called
Bridget Walsh because of
the Interpol warrant
that bears her name
for the bombings
of the London Tube.
She's a hero.
This here's Logan.
you'll remember him.
He's a history teacher from
Boston. long-time sympathizer.
I have family in Belfast.
It's an honor to meet you.
And that's Donal.
who you've met.
He's from Derry.
He came over with me.
He's an explosive expert. apparently.
Careful there. Donal.
As long as nobody sneezes.
I'm all right.
Cheers. Bridget.
That's Mary.
She's from Hell's Kitchen.
I've seen you speak at NORAID.
Is she joining us?
To Mary's point...
they've all taken the oath
of loyalty
to the Irish Republican Army.
Any objections?
The loyalty oath.
Yeah. I know it well.
Do you have a gun
and a Bible handy?
Yeah. we do.
[tense music]
[officer]
Come on. Let's go.
Move.
Watch your head.
-Appreciate it.
-[car door shutting]
Moira. don't worry.
It's what's best for the boy.
Guess she's not a fan of yours.
-[applause]
-Thank you.
This is very humbling.
Wow. 1980.
Time flies.
Especially you get to be my age.
[crowd laughing]
[clears throat]
My father left me two things...
that are very important to me.
His rosary...
and a debt
that I never got to repay...
until tonight.
That debt was not money.
It was the price of keepin'
our name outta the gutter
and our heads above the water.
I. Sarah McKenna.
AKA Bridget Walsh.
do solemnly swear
in the presence of Almighty God
and my comrades in arms
to uphold and protect
the Irish Republican Army
with all that I have
and all I may ever be.
[Sweeney]
It's been paid by bricklayers
who drank their pain.
by proud Irish mothers
who scrubbed
other people's floors
so their sons wouldn't
have to steal.
It's been paid
in favors and funerals.
In silence...
and in fists.
In blood we never bragged about.
We built this neighborhood.
And. yeah. we bled for it.
And we buried
more than a few good souls
to make sure we hold onto it.
I pledge obedience
without question
to follow commands.
to carry out justice.
to keep the secrets
of this cause
until my last breath
or until Ireland stands whole.
[Sweeney]
And we did it with pride
because we belong.
Tonight. we remember who we are.
And who we will never be.
We're not some
forgotten little tribe
in a tiny corner of Manhattan.
We Irish are its spine.
[Bridget]
I swear to fight. to suffer.
and. if called. to die...
for the dream
of a United Ireland.
Until the tricolor
flies in peace
from Belfast to Derry.
or I lie beneath it.
So help me God.
[Sweeney]
When I say thank you tonight.
I'm talking not only
about this lovely award.
[speaking Gaelic]
[Sweeney]
I'm talking about a legacy.
The kind you don't hang
on the wall.
a legacy you carry
in your heart.
It's in your bones.
And I promise you
right here and now.
long as I'm breathing.
nobody is gonna forget that
we Irish built
this neighborhood!
[cheering]
[♪ House of the Rising Sun ♪
[playing]
♪ I got one foot ♪
♪ On the platform ♪
♪ And another one ♪
♪ On the train ♪
♪ I'm going home ♪
♪ To New Orleans ♪
♪ To wear ♪
♪ That ball and chain ♪
[gurgling]
Looks like the Italians
weren't too happy
with you selling that coke.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
You wanna get a beer?
♪ And it's been the ruin ♪
♪ Of many a poor boy ♪
♪ And God ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ I'm one ♪
[♪ House of the Rising Sun ♪
[continues]
Subtitling: difuze
[police siren]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-